Delaney, Tom, Papers /4323
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Tom Delaney Papers
1979-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Delaney, Tom
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4323
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
9218938
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 14, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4164 AV: Harrison M. Trice Audio-Visual Materials
Delaney, Tom; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
9218938
- Archives, 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ad Hoc Public Relations Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Administration, 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Aerospace 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Al-Anon 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Alcohol and Drug Coalition 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Alcohol and Drug Problems Association 1984-1989 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Alcohol Drug Study Group 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Alcohol and Drugs in the Workplace 1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ALMACAN 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Use of ALMACAN Name and Logo 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Alcoholism Study Committee 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- American Civic Liberties Union 1986-1990 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- American Council on Alcoholism 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- American Journal of Health Promotion 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- American Medical Association, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- American Occupation Therapy Association 1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- American Petroleum Institute 1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- American Productivity Center 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- American Psychological Association 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- American Public Health Association 1988 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- American Restaurant Association 1987 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- American Society for Personnel Administrators 1982-1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- American Society for Public Administration 1987 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- American Society for Public Administrators 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- American Society on Aging, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Americans for Substance Abuse Prevention 1984 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Areba-Casriel Institute 1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Association for Fitness in Business 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Association of Halfway House Alcoholism Programs 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- The Association of Junior Leagues 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Association of Labor Assistance 1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Gary Atkins, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Board of Directors 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Board of Directors 1988 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Board of Directors 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Brooklyn Committee on Alcoholism, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Budgets and Finance Commission 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Bureau of National Affairs 1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Business Insurance 1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- California Public Policy 1984-1990 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Campus Alcohol Consultations 1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Canada 1987-1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Certification, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Chapter Presidents, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Children of Alcoholics 1986 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Cocaine 1990 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Communism on Accreditation of Rehabilitation Facilities 1989 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Committee on Insurance 1988, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- CompCare 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- The Conference Board 1986 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Confidentiality, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Coordinator or Education, Training, and Certification Interviews 1989 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- The Core Technology of Employee Assistance Programs 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Cornell/ILR, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Corporation Against Drug Abuse 1990 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Council on Accreditation of Services for Families and Children 1989 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Council on Alcohol Policy 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Drug Abuse Act Correspondence 1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- EAPA Role With Transportation Employees in Safety Sensitive Positions 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- EAP Association Planning Opposite 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Education and Training Committee 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Frank Emig 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Employee Assistance Programs 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Employee Assistance Society of North America 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Employer Coalitions 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Ethics, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Employee Retirement Income Security Act (ERISA) 1983-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Executive Committee 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Executive Committee 1987 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Executive 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Executive Committee 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Executive Director 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Executive 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Executive Director Reports, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Exxon Valdez 1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Federal Highway Administration 1988 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Federal Railroad Administration 1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Florida Occupational Program Committee 1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Fundraising 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Government Relations Director 1991 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Grace Church 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Health and Human Services, 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Hughes Foundation 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Institute for a Drug-Free Workplace 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Insurance 1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Intergovernmental Health Policy Project 1990 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Joint Commission Accreditation of Hospitals 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Legal, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Legal Action Center, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Legislative Committee 1988 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Legislative Committee 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Legislation Committee Correspondence 1986 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Liability Insurance 1984-1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Licensed Beverage Information Council 1986 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Managed Health Care 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- McDonnell Douglas 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Mentally Disabled/Ill, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Minority Concerns Committee 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- More Change Committee, 1983-1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- National "21" Drinking Age, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- National Academy of Sciences 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- National Alcohol and Drug Treatment Consortium 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- National Association of Alcohol Treatment Programs, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- National Association Area Agencies on Aging 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- National Association of Social Workers 1981-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- National Association of State Alcohol and Drug Abuse Directors 1980-1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- National Black Alcoholism Council 1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- National Citizens Commission on Alcoholism 1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- National Clearinghouse for Alcohol Information 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- National Coalition for Adequate Alcoholism Programs 1983-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- National Commission Against Drunk Driving 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- National Council of Alcoholism, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- National Council on Compulsive Gambling 1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- National Directorate for the Prevention of Alcohol on Drug Problems, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- National Directory 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- National Education Development and Training Center 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- National Employee Assistance Service 1987 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- National Episcopal Coalition of Alcohol and Drugs, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- National Federation of Societies for Clinical Social Work 1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- National Foundation for Prevention of Chemical Dependency Disease, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- National Institute on Alcoholism and Alcoholism Abuse, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- National Institute of Mental Health, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- National Institute on Drug Abuse 1987 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- National Management Analysis 1986 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- National treatment Consortium 1991 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- National Medical Enterprises 1987 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- National Partnership To Prevent Drug and Alcohol Abuse Amongst Youth 1986 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- National School Boards Association 1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- National Underwriter 1988 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- New York City Chapter 1987 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- NYS Commission on Quality of Cars For The Mentally Disabled 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- New York State Council on Alcoholism 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- NYS Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- New York State Legislature 1984-1989 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- North American Congress on Employee Assistance Programs 1988 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Occupation Program Consultants Association 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Office of Substance Abuse Program 1988 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- OSHA 1990 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Oxford House 1989 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- President's Drug Advisory Council 1991 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Prevention Leadership Forum 1990 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Public Policy 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Publishing Research 1984 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Reagan Executive Order: Drug-Free Federal Workplace 1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Regional Conference Guidelines, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Organization of Regions, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Central Regions, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Eastern Regions, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- International Region, 1986-1991 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Southern Region, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Western Region 1979-1988 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Running Amuk 1989 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Schenectady Gazette 1988 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Schools, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Secretary, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Security 1987 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Smithers Institute 1988 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- South Carolina, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- State University of New York 1989 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Transportation Workers 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- United Jersey Banks 1988 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- U.S. Department of Labor, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- U.S. House of Representatives Committee on Small Business 1991 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- U.S, Nuclear Regulatory Commission 1990 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- U.S. Senate 1988 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- University of California 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- University of Michigan 1988 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- University of Minnesota 1987 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Veteran's Administration 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Washington Area EAP's, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- White House Conference for a Drug-Free America 1987 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Wine Institute, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Work in America Institute 1988 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Worksite Assistance 1988 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Youth And Alcohol 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- News Clippings, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- News Clippings, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- News Clippings, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 78)